my-company-profile.com 2013-08-05

# Privacy Policy :: Company Profiles

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for My-Company-Profile.com.

We want to build your trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. We are committed to your privacy and are disclosing our information practices in this company statement.

This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only in effect for the Web pages, newsletters, discussion lists and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by My-Company-Profile.com.

**Collecting Information**

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer’s “Internet Protocol” IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within the My-Company-Profile.com Network, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor’s domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, but do not collect and evaluate this information for individuals. Our Web servers do not record e-mail addresses of the visitors.

**Use of Cookies**

From time to time, My-Company-Profile.com or its advertisers may send a “cookie” to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. A cookie can not read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of My-Company-Profile.com Network of Web pages you have visited, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you have seen an advertisement. We and our advertisers may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our site.

You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

**Information Request**

We may also request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a survey or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to e-mail newsletters, announcement lists or information about seminars) Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. We maintain a strict “No-Spam” policy, that means that we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent.

In addition, My-Company-Profile.com will not send you email that you have not agreed to receive. We may from time to time send e-mail announcing new My-Company-Profile.com products and services. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form, you may receive mailings from other reputable, third-party companies.

If you choose to purchase something online, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. This information may also be used by us to notify you of related product and services, but will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose.

**Disclose of Information to Outside Third Parties**

My-Company-Profile.com will disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:  
1\. Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on My-Company-Profile.com  
2\. Protect and defend the rights or property of My-Company-Profile.com, or visitors to My-Company-Profile.com  
3\. Identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties,  
4\. Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities. My-Company-Profile.com uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties which receive the information. My-Company-Profile.com also links to a wide variety of other sites and contains advertisements of third parties. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your email address), we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us. Please email information to sales at My-Company-Profile.com

**Newsletter**

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter or email updates, we ask for contact information such as first name and email address. This information is only used to send out the information requested. Names collected are not used at this time. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

**Choice/Opt-out**

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by sending an email to leave-cp@My-Company-Profile.com.  
Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.

**Information Collection and Use**

My-Company-Profile.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. My-Company-Profile.com presently collects information from its users at different points on its website as follows.

**Sharing Information**

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers if requested. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person or computer.

We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. If you do not want your personal information shared, please email support@My-Company-Profile.com with your request.

The parties listed above are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time our site may request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Your Consent To This Agreement**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by My-Company-Profile.com as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Copyright 2011**

All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy.
